aesoponline.com 2009-06-27

# Frontline Placement Technologies | Privacy Policy

privacy policy    
...................................................................................................................................................................  
The Internet is a powerful medium that allows communication all over the globe, quickly and easily. However, it requires protection and guidelines to be safe and secure. Frontline Placement Technologies, Inc., the owner and exclusive distributor of Aesop, is dedicated to providing you, the user, with a secure and useful experience on the Internet. Frontline Placement Technologies adheres to the following policies regarding your private information. 

**Frontline Placement Technologies, Inc. will not provide your information to a third party vendor.  
**We believe that your information is private, and as such we will not disclose information to any outside source. The information that you provide online will be sent to the school district(s) for which you work, but will not divulge any information to marketing groups or list vendors. 

**Frontline Placement Technologies, Inc. does provide security for online transactions.**

Frontline Placement Technologies, Inc. uses secure logon via SSL to prevent access to your information. Your login id and PIN is required to gain access to your personal information. Additionally, Frontline Placement Technologies, Inc. uses industry standard encryption protocols to safeguard your personal information in transit over the Internet. 

**Frontline Placement Technologies, Inc. is dedicated to following and enforcing our standards.**

We want to ensure that we are providing you with the level of security that you need, while still providing a useful interface to your personal information. If you have any questions, comments or issues pertaining to the adherence of Frontline Placement Technologies, Inc. to these policies, please e-mail the webmaster at [info@AesopOnline.com](mailto:info@AesopOnline.com). This email address is being protected from spam bots (you need Javascript enabled to view it) and you will need to include the words Privacy Policy in the subject of the e-mail.   

**  
Cookies**

A cookie is a data file that certain web sites write to your computer's hard drive when you visit such sites. A cookie file can contain information, such as a user identification code, that the site uses to maintain a personalized look and feel on the pages you have visited. AesopOnline.com uses cookies solely to maintain "members-only" access levels throughout the AesopOnline.com web site. We use this data on an anonymous basis and we do not correlate this information with personal data of any user. 

Most web site browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually change your browser settings to display a warning before accepting a cookie, or to refuse all cookies. However, if you choose to disable the receipt of cookies from our web site, you may not be able to use certain features of the site. 

**Browser Level Information**

AesopOnline.com web servers automatically collect information about a site user's IP address, browser type and referrer by reading this information from the user's browser (information provided by every user's browser). This information is collected in a database and used--in an aggregated, anonymous manner--in our internal analysis of traffic patterns within our web site. This information is automatically logged by most web sites. 

**Definitions**

**IP address:** Every computer connected to the Internet has a numeric address called an "IP address." This may or may not correspond uniquely to a particular computer. In some cases, IP addresses can be resolved to domain names, which may indicate a site visitor's Internet service provider, employer, university, etcetera. As part of its database analysis AesopOnline.com resolves IP addresses to domain names. 

**Browser type:** A user's browser is a software program running on a computer that allows users to access documents on the World Wide Web. Browsers can be either text or graphic. They read HTML coded pages that reside on a server and interpret the coding into what the user sees as Web pages. Netscape Navigator and Microsoft Internet Explorer are examples of Web browsers. Browser type typically discloses hardware platform, operating system, and browser software and version. 

Referrer: The referrer is the URL of the Internet resource or page that causes a browser to request a page or image from AesopOnline.com servers.
